Uh...
Welcome, huh?
Wait! Let me do it.
I'll do it.
Wait here, okay?
Just sit there and look pretty.
I'll handle it since
you're a guest.
There.
Okay...
And now you do this.
Just pour a little into the cap.
Then you just throw it away.
What the...?
That's what you call
an offering to the devil.
Or in English... sorry.
- A sacrifice to the devil.
- [OMINOUS STING]
A sacrifice to who?
Because, sir,
if you don't do that,
the devil might come with you.
Also known as...
- [EVIL LAUGHTER]
- [CHUCKLES]
Okay!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Geonbae.
Cheers.
Geonbae!
[GLASSES CLINK]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mmh.
Oh.
Sir, what's the
Korean word for...
...shot glass?
- Jan.
- Oh, here?
Jan.
Oh, jan.
How about...
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
...bed?
Chimdae.
Chimdae?
How about...
...love?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Saranghae.
Saranghae... too.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]